fineartamerica.com 2018-06-15

# Terms of Use - Fine Art America

Effective May 25th, 2018

Our privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") describes how information and data is collected from you when you use our website, mobile app, or any related products and services (each a "Service", collectively the "Services") and how Fine Art America ("we", "us", and "our") uses, shares, and manages your information and data. By using any of our Services, you consent to the collection, use, processing, and sharing of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

## Information that We Collect From You

### Information Collected Voluntarily from Registered Users

If you register as a user of our Services, we may collect and process the following information from you:

  * Name
  * E-Mail Address
  * Password
  * Mailing Address
  * Phone Number

### Additional Information Collected Voluntarily from Sellers

If you register as a seller, you may be asked to provide us with additional information in order to receive monthly profit payments from us. We may collect and process the following information from you:

  * Paypal E-Mail Address
  * Federal Tax Identification Number

After opening an account to sell on Fine Art America, a seller is able to create a public profile page and upload information and content to the page that is intended for public consumption, including, but not limited to: the seller's name, hometown, biography, headshot, images, and more. Any website visitor that visits Fine Art America and navigates to the seller's profile page will be able to view all of the public profile information that has been entered by the seller. This information is managed the seller and can be modified by the seller at any time.

### Information Collected Voluntarily via our Support Channels

If you contact us via one of our support channels (e.g. customer service / technical support), we may collect and process the following information:

  * Name
  * E-Mail Address
  * Phone Number
  * Customer Service and/or Technical Information Provided by You

### Information Collected Voluntarily from E-Mail Subscribers

If you sign up to receive e-mails from Fine Art America, we may collect and process the following information:

  * Name
  * E-Mail Address
  * Phone Number
  * Customer Service and/or Technical Information Provided by You

### Information Collected at Checkout

If you purchase an item through our Services, we may collect and process the following information:

  * Name
  * E-Mail
  * Phone Number
  * Billing Address
  * Shipping Address
  * Credit Card Data
  * Paypal E-Mail Address
  * Order Details (e.g. items purchased, prices, quantities, etc.)

For any transactions on Fine Art America that require a credit card or debit card, Fine Art America stores the last four digits of the credit/debit card number, the expiration date, and the buyer's name. We do NOT store the full credit card number, pin number, CVV2 number, or any full-track data.

### Public Data Posted by You

If you post information on the public areas of our Services, the information will be collected by us and may be used by us, other users, and the general public. Examples of publicly posted information include, but are not limited to: biographies, comments, discussion forum posts, group messages, and product reviews.

### Information Collected Automatically

In addition to the information that you voluntarily provide to us, our Services may collect and process additional data, automatically. This information may include:

  * Device Identification Data (e.g. type of device, IP address, operating system, browser type, etc.)
  * Device Settings (e.g. language preferences)
  * Location Data (e.g. longitude / latitude)
  * Requested URLs (the Service pages that you visit)
  * Referring URLs (the previous URL that brought you to our Services)
  * Usage Data (e.g. how often you use our Services, which products you view, etc.)

## How We Use Your Information

### Improving Our Services, Providing Support, Communicating with You, and Processing Orders

Fine Art America and our service providers may use the data collected from you to:

  * improve our Services
  * provide you with customer service and/or technical support
  * communicate with you
  * process and ship your orders

## How We Share Your Information

### Payment Processing

We may share your information with payment processors (e.g. Visa, Mastercard, American Express, Paypal, etc.) for the purposes of processing payments from you.

### Order Processing

We may share your information with our fulfillment partners in order to process your ordered products, ship the products to your destination addresses, and provide you customer service and technical support.

### Data Analytics

We may share your information with third-party analytics companies ("Analytics Services") such as Google Analytics in order to track and analyze your use of our Services. These Analytics Services collect information about the content that you view along with actions that you take (e.g. adding an item to a shopping cart) while using our Services. The information generated by the Analytics Services about your use of our Services is transmitted to and stored by the Analytics Services.

### Advertising

We may share your information with advertisers, advertising networks, and analytics companies who may use the information to deliver targeted advertisements to you through our Services or through third-party websites or advertisers. These advertisers may share information with us about you that they have independently gathered or acquired.

### Service Providers

We may share your information with service providers who work on our behalf. For example, we may share your information with service providers that handle customer service, order fulfillment, e-mail marketing, data analysis, market research, and more. Each service provider is only given access to the information that is necessary to perform these functions on our behalf.

### Legal Requirements

To the extent permitted by law, we will disclose your information to government authorities or third parties, including national security or law enforcement agencies, if required to do so by law.

### Terms of Use Violations

We may disclose your information to government authorities or third parties, including national security or law enforcement agencies, if we believe in our sole and absolute discretion that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect against fraud, to protect the property or other rights of us or other users, third parties or the public at large, or we believe that you have abused the Services by using it to attack other systems or to gain unauthorized access to any other system, to engage in spamming or otherwise to violate applicable laws or in violation of our Terms of Use. Following disclosure to any third party, your information may be accessible by others to the extent permitted or required by applicable law.

### Business Transfers

In the event of a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of our assets or any business, any user information owned or controlled by us may be one of the assets transferred to third parties in such transaction or event. We reserve the right, as part of this type of transaction or event, to transfer or assign your information and other information we have collected from users of the Services to third parties.

## How Long We Store Your Information

We store your information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for the information was collected or, if the law provides for longer retention periods, for the duration of the retention period required by law.

## Information Security

Fine Art America takes precautions to ensure that private user information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect information that is stored within our databases, and we restrict access to private information to those employees and service providers who need access to perform their job functions. No method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of your personal information.

## Your Access and Control of Your Information

To request access to or correction of your personal information, you may send an e-mail to privacy@fineartamerica.com or a letter to:

Fine Art America

ATTN: Legal Department

2202 Main Street

Santa Monica, CA 90405

If you would like us to delete information that you have provided through the Services, please contact us at privacy@fineartamerica.com. Please note that some or all of the information collected may be required in order for the Services to function properly or may be automatically retained in backup / archival storage. You may not be able to use the Services if this information is deleted.

## Use of Cookies

Fine Art America uses cookies to operate our Services and store information which helps us personally identify return users of our Services.

## Third-Party Websites and Apps

Our Services allow sellers to offer their products for sale through third-party websites and applications such as Facebook, Shopify, and Amazon. Fine Art America is not responsible for and has no control over how these apps and websites function and their respective privacy policies.

## Links

Fine Art America contains links to other websites. Fine Art America is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on those other websites. When linking to another website, a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on Fine Art America.

## Changes in Our Privacy Policy

From time to time, Fine Art America may make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so that they will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. Users are bound by changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted.

## Contacting Fine Art America

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at privacy@fineartamerica.com.
